fruitkingsplaza.com 2016-02-25

# Our Privacy policy:

**Our Privacy policy:**

_**INTRODUCTION**_

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website, fruitkingsplaza.com 

_**PERSONAL INFORMATION**_

In order to use this site and any of our affiliated sites, you must complete the registration form attached, providing your personal information and at the same time creating a user name and password. Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an e-mail address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. This information is used to generate reports on the overall traffic to the site for bandwith planning and usage statistics. 

Wherever your Personal Information may be held by us, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. 

We strive to comply with applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, we intend to adhere to the principles set forth in this Privacy Statement. 

_**COOKIES**_

Some of our Web pages utilize “cookies” and other tracking technologies. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Web site activity and is used to ensure that private information associated with your registered account stays private and viewable only to you. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web site and your Web experience. We may analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords so you do not have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter the original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Web site. 

_**ACCEPTABLE USE**_

Use of this website content is prohibited unless agreed to by **Fruitkingsplaza** prior. Any third party affiliate found using this website or the contents thereof to spam will be shut down 

_**SURVEYS AND CONTESTS**_

From time to time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on-site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. 

_**SPECIAL OFFERS AND UPGRADES**_

We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals and promotions. You can sign up for these e-mails from us on our registration page. 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by sending an e-mail to no_news@fruitkingsplaza.com

_**CHANGES TO PRIVACY STATEMENT**_

We will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. When we post changes to this Statement, you will see the word “updated” next to the Privacy Statement link on the front page of our Web site. If there are any material changes to this Statement or in how we will use your personal information, we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. We encourage you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how we are protecting your information. 

_**CONTACT INFORMATION**_

We welcome your comments regarding this Privacy Statement. If you have any questions about this Statement or believe we have not adhered to it, please contact us at Privacy@fruitkingsplaza.com
